

■ nmhkahn@gmail.com | 🎓 nmhkahn.github.io | 🛅 nmhkahn | 🞓 Namhyuk Ahn

Research Interest

My research goal is to develop powerful generative AI (Gen AI) solutions applicable across various domains, creating a strong Gen AI+X framework. I am currently focused on creating specialized methodologies to adapt large-scale foundational Gen AI models in fields such as media, art, healthcare, manufacturing, and logistics, although my scope is not limited to these areas. I am also interested in exploring the societal implications of Gen Als and developing ways to mitigate potential negative impacts that may arise from the development of Gen AI.

### Work Experience \_

**Inha University** Incheon, Korea

ASSISTANT PROFESSOR

AI RESEARCHER

Sep. 2024 - Present

Aug. 2021 - Aug. 2024

- School of Electrical and Electronics Engineering
- Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering (Graduate School)

NAVER WERTOON Pangyo, Korea

- Built user-centric Al tools designed for cartoon creators/artists (e.g. Cartooner, DreamStyler)
- Researched user privacy-aware Gen AI (e.g. Impasto, which prevents copyright violation by Gen AI models)
- Developed portrait stylization production (e.g. WebtoonMe)

**NAVER AI LAB** Bundang, Korea

VISITING RESEARCHER

Sep. 2019 - Oct. 2020

- Researched data augmentation for image super-resolution (e.g. CutBlur)
- Developed label-efficient conditional generative models
- Co-worked with Jaejun Yoo, Youngjung Uh and Yunjey Choi

**NAVER** Bundang, Korea

June 2018 - Aug. 2018

· Developed image-to-image translation pipeline for talking head project

#### Education

INTERN

**Ajou University** Suwon, Korea

Ph.D. IN ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE Mar. 2016 - Aug. 2021

- Advisor: Prof. Kyung-Ah Sohn
- Thesis: Toward an Efficient Deep Image Restoration Method

**Ajou University** Suwon, Korea

BACHELOR OF MEDIA IN DIGITAL MEDIA Mar. 2012 - Aug. 2016

### **Selected Publication**

Namhyuk Ahn, Wonhyuk Ahn, KiYoon Yoo, Daesik Kim, Seung-Hun Nam. Imperceptible Protection Against Style Imitation from Diffusion Models. preprint arXiv:2403.19254

Namhyuk Ahn, Jaejun Yoo, Kyung-Ah Sohn. Data Augmentation for Low-Level Vision: CutBlur and Mixture-of-Augmentation. IJCV24

Namhyuk Ahn, Junsoo Lee, Chunggi Lee. Kunhee Kim, Daesik Kim, Seung-Hun Nam, Kibeom Hong. DreamStyler: Paint by Style Inversion with Text-to-Image Diffusion Models. AAAI24

Kibeom Hong, Seogkyu Jeon, Junsoo Lee, Namhyuk Ahn, Kunhee Kim, Pilhyeon Lee, Daesik Kim, Youngjung Uh, Hyeran Byun. AesPA-Net: Aesthetic Pattern-Aware Style Transfer Networks. ICCV23

Namhyuk Ahn, Patrick Kwon, Jihye Back, Kibeom Hong, Seungkwon Kim. Interactive Cartoonization with Controllable Perceptual Factors. CVPR23 Namhyuk Ahn, Byungkon Kang, Kyung-Ah Sohn. Efficient Deep Neural Network for Photo-realistic Image Super-Resolution. PR22

Jaejun Yoo\*, Namhyuk Ahn\*, Kyung-Ah Sohn. Rethinking Data Augmentation for Image Super-resolution: A Comprehensive Analysis and a New

Namhyuk Ahn, Byungkon Kang, Kyung-Ah Sohn. Fast, Accurate, and Lightweight Super-Resolution with Cascading Residual Network. ECCV18

# **Professional Service**

**Reviewer** CVPR (2023-2024), ICCV (2023), ECCV (2024), NeurIPS (2024)

TPAMI, IJCV, TIP, TMM, TCSVT, SPIC, ESWA

**Editor** Mathematical Biosciences and Engineering (2022-2023; Guest)

# **Teaching**.

**2024-2** Computer Graphics, Creative Design for ICE

**2017** Deep Learning and its Applications (at FastCampus)

# Invited Talk\_

**2024.5** Ajou University, "Career path advise for undergraduate students"

**2023.3** Ajou University, "Recent advances in visual generative models"